

Mob : +91 8512002866 Email : sainikunal581@gmail.com

About

Interaction and Motion Designer Professional with 2+ year of experience in User Interface & experience design with an in-depth understanding interface and interaction. Expert in providing quick solutions to maximize results. Good communication with teams and understand problems. Give a smart and qualitative work in a sprints time.

Portfolio link

Behance Link: https://www.behance.net/sainikunal3bee

Experience

Р

Product Designer

GLEAC

October 2019 - Present (6 months)



UI Designer

Venuemonk

December 2018 - October 2019



UI Designer/Motion

MysteryMonk

September2017 - December 2018



Graphic Designer (Intern)

Bridge Impact

January 2017 - August 2017 (6 months)

Education



Arena Animation

Communication Design

January 2015 - August 2017



Empathy in UX Design

LinkedIn

Issued Feb 2020 . No Expiration Date

Skills

Hard Skills

- Interaction Design
 Sitemap
 User flow
 Flow prototype
 Low-High fidelity wireframes
- User reserachGraphics

Soft Skills

Communication
 Leadership
 Critical Thinker
 Team building